(Sheldon:)Would you pass
the mustard?
(Leonard:)Sure.
(Leonard:)Hey, want to hear
a fun fact about mustard?
(Sheldon:)Is it that the glucosinolates
which give mustard its flavor
(Sheldon:)were evolved
by the cabbage family
as a chemical defense
against caterpillars?
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Well, that was fun.
(Sheldon:)Good for you, Leonard.
(Raj(entering with Howard):)Hey, there.
(Leonard:)Hey, you're early.
(Leonard:)The movie doesn't start
for an hour.
(Howard:)Actually, we're not
going to the movies.
(Howard:)We are here to kidnap you.
(Leonard:)What are you talking about?
(Raj:)Well, you eloped and
we didn't get a chance
(Raj:)to throw you
a bachelor party,
(Raj:)so there's
a van downstairs
(Raj:)and we're here
to take you
(Raj:)to a surprise location
for the weekend.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'd hardly
call this kidnapping.
(Sheldon:)Where's the blindfold?
(Sheldon:)Where's the duct tape?
(Sheldon:)Where's the part
(Sheldon:)where you call me
and demand ransom
(Sheldon:)and I try to keep you
on the phone,
(Sheldon:)but you hang up
seconds before I can trace it
and then I say, "I'm getting
too old for this crud"?
(Leonard:)When do we leave?
(Howard:)Right now.
(Raj:)Yeah, Penny packed
you a bag.
(Howard:)Wow, okay.
(Sheldon:)You're seriously going to get
in a van and let these two
(Raj:)take you
to an unknown destination
(Sheldon:)for an entire weekend?
Oh, not just him;
you're coming, too.
(Sheldon:)Oh, and how do you think you're
going to get me to do that?
Unhand me!
This is ridiculous!
(Howard:)I told you to put tape
on his mouth!
And I told you he bit me!
♪Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪